this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them now this sight can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course
awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
after being separated from his crew luffy set out to rescue his captured brother
ace to do so he snuck into the government prison impelled down
buggy and mr. three who were desperately trying to make their way to freedom
had been captured by hymnobal
meanwhile luffy's battle against warden magellan had reached a dire outcome
consider this your punishment child there's no way to neutralize the amount of poison your body has
absorbed you will suffer an agonizing pain for 24 hours and then you will die this is true hell
for his breath bonkley's deadly rescue attempt
warden magellan excellent battle sir what should we do with luffy any orders he'll die soon but we
don't want him just lying there throw him into the central tower of level five until further notice
yes sir warden magellan bad news sir there's a problem over at the staircase to level three
that's the area hennobal and his men we're guarding what's happening there i don't know the details sir
hey hey guess he's gone he's either stone cold dead or hibernating for the winter
sounds nice damn my fingers are shot i can't move them i can't even feel them sounds like frostbite
sorry your history
i can't even bite my stinking bread can we stop by the burning hell for a sec
check it out they're dragging in a newbie sucks to be him
hey pal what's your name how much is your bounty worth come on talk to us
looks like he's nearly dead magellan's already given him a taste of his poison
i leave for a moment and this is what i return to
and you let me down
wake up you imbecile what the hell happened here
i was cut off guard i'm sorry sir
no don't torture us torture stinks like ass and by the way mine is very sensitive so please
don't whip it some nutty martial artist ballerina did all this i'll be frank with you he took
us by surprise sir silence no excuses you let him slip away and he escaped to the upper levels
didn't he it seems that prisoner used to be part of crocodile's baroque works he's the one who used
to call himself mr two he's rather odd i don't care at any rate i wouldn't worry sir i feel confident
that we'll catch him in time and what of the riot on level two any updates it's winding down almost
under control sir i want all the guards on level four to proceed to level three immediately i also
want all of mr sadie's demon guard searching for the escapee i'll leave the rest to you right and what
about these two sir do as you like just make sure this mess is all cleaned up and things are in order
by the time i get back i'm going to head over to my private place for a bit
oh my tummy oh the runs hey move it get off your asses we still have one last escapee we need to
track down yes right away sir um excuse me vice warden what do you want to do with these two
oh i want to ask them a few questions get an interrogation room i'll take charge of them
personally right understood sir i'll make the preparations
okay then they're all yours right
so far so good wouldn't you say
too easy yes no one's whipping my buttocks tonight
okay that's that now what do we do don't play it down you know what's next we need to hurry up and
rescue straw hat before it's too late you're still hung up on that didn't you hear them saying that
he's been poisoned by magellan and taken to level five it's too late to save him there's no way he'll
survive and will be caught tortured and die like dogs it's a bad plan why should we risk our lives
to save someone who's as good as dead that won't stop me i'll gladly die like a dog for him after
turning my back on straw boy i'm already dead inside the least i can do is make things right
i thought that it was better to run and save myself than to suffer the same fate but i swore
that if there was any chance he would survive i'd return put my life on the line and rescue him
and i meant it so i must come to his aid yeah that's a real touching story but now you've escaped
you're almost a free man why would you want to go back out there guns a-blazin and risk your life again
because i'm his friend i don't need any other reason that's it
first we gotta deal with that poison there's surely they have some sort of antidote but then
where would it be you think there's still time to get an antidote nah i wouldn't bother shut up already
both of you this is something this is something i have to do don't die on me straw boy hold on a
little bit longer no freaking way i mean uh what do you mean you can't make an antidote what is the
hold up no one ever survives after warden magellan douses them with that much of his special attack
if it was just one kind of poison maybe but his is a special multi-faceted toxin there are just too
many variables to account for i'm afraid it's impossible vice warden what the you're kidding and
you people call yourselves a medical team lies huh i mean the answer lies ahead just keep trying we
have to turn straw hat luffy over to the navy and i want him alive for that but even if we think we're
on to a cure if we administer any sort of medication incorrectly he'll most likely die even sooner
i told you it's hopeless let it go and move on you heard them there is no antidote you'd be
throwing your life away for nothing now let go of that nonsense and think about escaping let's find
a way out of here together he's right you need to learn when to give up my friend we'll melt away
if we stay here very much longer you gotta face it no matter how hard you may try straw hats past the
point of no return understand it was reckless of him to go head to head against magellan in the first
place there's a reason he has such a fearful reputation no one survives a battle with him it
would take a miracle a miracle oh yeah i forgot about him he's in impel down my hero the miracle worker
when doctors give up on a patient he can still save them he can even save a dying country his list of
miracles is legendary he's the greatest the queen of all queens eva come on we need to find out where
they're holding him now we need to what
sir level five yep that's where we're headed prisoner transfer these two were sentenced to freeze to death
what the hell is he doing why are we going down what choice do we have we could try to escape on our
own but by now the security on level three has been tightened by order of magellan himself we'll
never get past that many guards we're safer like this for now as long as we stay with the vice warden
we can at least move around without any hassle look i know that but his obsession with saving straw hat
is going to be the end of us we can't keep this up forever you know yes but perhaps a plan b will present
itself in time
keep walking scumbers i realize this is a bit of a long shot but i have to do anything i can
this list of prisoners is presenting more questions than it's answering i'm afraid like this for example
emporio ivankov the real name of eva has been crossed off in red ink has he been released
already or has he been secretly executed tell me something did we let this prisoner go free what
oh you mean ivankov you know what happened to him a few years ago you know what wait vice warden you
forgot huh oh yeah of course i remember now let's see if you know huh but there are prisoners present
sir i don't care out with it every so often people disappear in impel town we're sure they didn't just
break out as some of the missing could barely move they just vanished without a trace and no one seems to
know the cause we've come to call it demon in the way all the guards here have come to fear these
unnatural and strange disappearances we believe that those missing have been dragged to the gates
of hell hence why we call it what we do so people just up and vanish
creepy i wish i'd never heard that yes same here
the door's not even open and it's already freezing and we're even wearing heavy clothes
this is it as a fair warning the army wolves are quite hungry today
now i'll take them from this point on just as usual huh you'll take what well your weapons and coats
sir huh honestly sir we don't know how you do it you always tell us i'll show every single prisoner
the courage of the vice warden and then march forward into the freezing hell without a weapon or even a
coat sincerely we're big admirers of you for it no way also because they're inappropriate for
prisoners to have we'll be taking their coats as well now hand them over our coats too
you say what right take care now and don't forget transponder snails won't work thanks to the cold and
all safe travels
why
i can barely use my hand it's so cold it feels like the wind watching me in the maze hold on i've
almost got it it's unlocked yes you did it thank you
one two three four hey don't tell me these aren't army wolves are they but why shouldn't they be on
the floor of the wild beasts from hell uh what do you mean oh i think i know why they're not it's
because they would eat the other beast like the basilisk in the sphinx it's for their protection
no way these mangy little fleabags are really that dangerous
you're gonna deal with these damn things too the cold was bad enough now i've got another reason for
my teeth to chatter
i want to fight make it quick because i've got a straw boy i need to say
i'm coming to save you time to show these wolves
a power that transcends gender
i can't move i'm frozen stiff
you still want to stick with that guy because he's nothing but a popsicle for wolves right now
i admit i didn't think the situation would go off the deep end quite so thoroughly we need to find a
way out of here now if we don't move those army wolves are gonna find us and rip us limb to limb
i know i complained a lot back at the burning heat hill but frankly i think this may be even worse
and that's not counting the wolves i'm getting tired hey keep running keep running
but i can't keep this running up forever it keeps me warm but it drains all my energy is you said
they've done since we've been at this for so long but let's try to devise a plan before our boys please
too how can it get
oh look a jail cell how that we can avoid the wind inside there
the wind isn't blowing here but the floor froze my butt and now i'm even colder
if we stick around we'll freeze head to toe we gotta come up with something and quick
right let's do it wait a sec you've got a plan what think back you remember when we formed that
lines to break out of here don't you we huddled and joined forces let's huddle again that's it
good we can snuggle up close to get nice and toasty
okay
damn i'm not getting any warmer at all and this is gross now that is just hurtful
yeah enough let's find a way out of here that's fine by me
what you're kidding they followed us and now there's even more of them
what are you saying i'm a wax man i'll taste absolutely dreadful
Yeah, the yummy one is this guy!
Whoa.
Come on, this is messed up.
Do we really have to sit here and just watch this kid die?
I have to save him! He's the only brother I've got!
You'll be nothing more than a leaf whipped about by a storm.
An insect flicked away by hands far mightier than your own.
Ah.
Ah!
No!
Ace!
Stop fighting it already.
Listen, you can't survive after taking that much poison.
I'm sure you can't see.
But can you at least hear me?
Just accept your death graciously.
I won't!
No!
Look!
I'm not gonna die till I rescue Ace!
How do you expect to save somebody
when you can't even save yourself?
Who is it anyway?
Some friend of yours?
How stupid.
In prison, it's every man for himself, got it?
No one's coming to help you.
That's just the way things are.
We're all alone down here.
In the Sea of Fire,
you'd trample all over someone else
in order to stay alive.
When you face the Beast,
you'd kick another prisoner
straight into their hungry jaws.
You'll die if you care about anyone but yourself.
So cut all the
I-wanna-rescue-someone crap.
Understand?
That talk makes me sick.
Look, somebody's coming.
I don't recognize him.
He's not one of the jailers.
Wait a minute.
Is he-
Nakin?
Strawboy, I've come here to rescue you!
In the name of our everlasting friendship!
Bon Clay wanders through level five
in search of the mysterious missing prisoner,
Ivanhoff.
However, the army wolves
and bitter cold
eventually take their toll
and he collapses
from exhaustion
in the freezing hell.
With Luffy's life
dwindling away,
who is left to save him?
On the next
One Piece
of Paradise and Hell
Impel Down Level 5.5
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!